<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Experiences on Dustin Dos Santos - Resume</title><link>https://muffinman989.github.io/cvsite/experiences/</link><description>Recent content in Experiences on Dustin Dos Santos - Resume</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://muffinman989.github.io/cvsite/experiences/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://muffinman989.github.io/cvsite/experiences/area/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://muffinman989.github.io/cvsite/experiences/area/</guid><description>A tech startup company focusing on three key products for venue experiences.
Products Under Develpment: Ticketure a ticking solution for venue staff and vistors TicketKit a proximity based marketing and analytical experiences toolkit STQRY a application designed to allow people to explore venues. References: Website: https://nz.linkedin.com/company/stqry</description></item><item><title/><link>https://muffinman989.github.io/cvsite/experiences/default/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://muffinman989.github.io/cvsite/experiences/default/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://muffinman989.github.io/cvsite/experiences/outsource/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://muffinman989.github.io/cvsite/experiences/outsource/</guid><description> A games company focusing on mobile and web based games directly to the consumer market. The focus was in maintaining and implementing additional features for existing games.
Games Under Development Small Worlds BloodGate References LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/company/outsmart-2005-ltd/?originalSubdomain=nz Youtube (Small Worlds): https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1AWO68nMA9k Steam (BloodGate): https://steamcommunity.com/app/464470/ GG Website (BloodGate): https://gg.deals/games/developed-by-outsmart/ Website (Company): http://www.outsmartgames.com/</description></item><item><title/><link>https://muffinman989.github.io/cvsite/experiences/samsung/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://muffinman989.github.io/cvsite/experiences/samsung/</guid><description>The role involved reading white papers implementing state of the art algorithms with a graphics/computer vision solutions often involving ML for PC and mobile platforms.
Frame Interpolation A ML model deisgned to generate a predictive frame given a sequence of previous frames within realtime frame rates.
Experiment with CNN based U-Net Architectures Profile models on Device for realtime performance Vulkan Proof of Concept (POC) for shared NPU memory References GitHub: https://liuziwei7.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://muffinman989.github.io/cvsite/experiences/xpi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://muffinman989.github.io/cvsite/experiences/xpi/</guid><description> The role involved developing a virtual enviornment for civilian and millitary training applications.
Unity based virtual environments with training instructions networked accross multiple machines and specialized hardware similar to train drivers in a simulator. References Website (Company): https://xpisimulation.com/</description></item></channel></rss>